netmedia101.com 2018-06-21

# Privacy Policy | NetMedia101

## ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AGREEMENT

NetMedia101,LLC, (NetMedia101), is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate,confidential,secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with NetMedia101,LLC of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.  
THEREFORE, this Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to NetMedia101,LLC , and thus it shall govern  
any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of http://www.NetMedia101.com you are  
herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.

## Collection of Information:

It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any  
website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.

## Use of Information Collected:

NetMedia101,LLC may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of  
our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it  
necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from http://www.NetMedia101.com .  
NetMedia101,LLC may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research  
questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.  
NetMedia101,LLC does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties.  
NetMedia101,LLC may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:

  * Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any  
process which may be served upon NetMedia101,LLC and/or our website.
  * Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of NetMedia101,LLC; and
  * Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of  
http://www.NetMedia101.com and/or the general public.

## Children Under Age of 13:

NetMedia101,LLC does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under  
the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.

## Unsubscribe or Opt-Out:

All users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to  
NetMedia101@gmail.com. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you  
must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.

## Links to Other Web Sites:

Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites. NetMedia101,LLC does not claim nor  
accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites.  
Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.

## Security:

NetMedia101,LLC shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical,  
procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user’s personal information under our control.

## Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement:

NetMedia101,LLC reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as  
such we will post those change to our website homepage at http://www.NetMedia101.com, so that our  
users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time  
NetMedia101,LLC decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner  
vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.

## Acceptance of Terms:

Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions,then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.

## How to Contact Us:

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website,  
please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.  
Email: NetMedia101@gmail.com  
Mailing Address:  
NetMedia101,LLC  
1483 Shore Parkway , 5A  
Brooklyn, New York 11214  
05/05/2017
